<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Montessori Albums</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Montessori Albums</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2023. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Culture</title>
      <link>http://example.org/album/culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/album/culture/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art Music Movement</title>
      <link>http://example.org/album/art_music_movement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/album/art_music_movement/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Language</title>
      <link>http://example.org/album/language/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/album/language/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Numbers Section.2.1.22</title>
      <link>http://example.org/album/math-intro-num/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/album/math-intro-num/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents Introduction to Numbers Red &amp;amp; Blue Number Rods Sandpaper Numerals Number Rods and Numerals Spindle Boxes Numerals and Counters Numeral Line Cards and Counters Memory Game Introduction to Numbers Red &amp;amp; Blue Number Rods Materials: Ten rods, graded in length, with the shortest at ten centimeters long (“one”) and with alternating painted sections of red and blue.
Prerequisites: The child should have worked with the red rods, be familiar with hearing the language of numerals &amp;amp; one-to-one correspondence, and have skills of grasping, grading, balance, and coordination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pre-Math and Early Math Exercises Section.1.22</title>
      <link>http://example.org/album/math-pre-math/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/album/math-pre-math/</guid>
      <description>Updated 12.2021
Table of Contents Pre-Math Math Activities (before 1-10) Logical Quantification Building Sets using Multiple Attributes Subitizing Patterning Supplemental Math Activities (after 1-10) Graphing Parts and Wholes Equivalencies (Exchange Games) Number Path Games Pre-Math Math Activities (before 1-10) The Pre-Math/Early Math Exercise shelf in the math area is placed after the Sensorial exercises, but before the red and blue rods. The activities do not typically emphasize numbers but do allow practice of foundational mathematical ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Decimal System Section.2.18.22</title>
      <link>http://example.org/album/math-decimal-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/album/math-decimal-system/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math</title>
      <link>http://example.org/album/math/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/album/math/</guid>
      <description>Pre-Math
Introduction to Numbers
The Decimal System
[](&amp;ldquo;UWRF 2021 STUDY OF ADDITION Math Album Section v2.docx&amp;rdquo;)
[](&amp;ldquo;UWRF 2021 STUDY OF SUBTRACTION Section of Math Album v2.docx&amp;rdquo;)
[](&amp;ldquo;UWRF 2021 STUDY OF MULTIPLICATION Math Album Section v2 (1).docx&amp;rdquo;)
[](&amp;ldquo;UWRF 2021 STUDY OF DIVISION Section of Math Album.docx&amp;rdquo;)
[](&amp;ldquo;UWRF 2021 STUDY OF FRACTIONS Section of Math Album.docx&amp;rdquo;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Childhood: Sensorial Album</title>
      <link>http://example.org/album/sensorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/album/sensorial/</guid>
      <description>montessoricompass.com
Submitted to Patricia Castillo Graduate Faculty of University of Wisconsin River Falls Course Dates: June-August 2021
Created by: Stephanie Thompson, 1340 Orange Street, River Falls, WI 715-977-0686 stephanie.thompson@myuwrf.edu Early Childhood Sensorial Album
Table of Contents Sensorial Rationale References INTRODUCTION TO SENSORIAL Sensorial Class Notes: Day 1: Sensorial In-Person Class Day 2: Sensorial Day 3 Notes: Lecture 10: Unlocking the Intelligence: Cylinders: Pink Tower, Broad Stair, Long Rods: Broad Stair Pink Tower: Indirect Preparation: Practical Life: Spooning Pros and Cons List: Video 1: Transferring with a Ladle : Video 2: Water Pouring Exercise 1: Sense of Touch Exploration of the Sense of Touch in Nature Exploring the Five Senses in Nature Journal Sensorial Album Notes: The Montessori Method: Chapters 12 and 13 Notes Chapter 12: Education of the Senses: Chapter 13: Education of the Senses and Illustrations of the Didactic Material: General Sensibility, the Tactile, Thermic, Baric, and Stereognostic Senses: Sensory Processing Video: A Child’s View of Sensory Processing: The Discovery of the Child: Chapters 9 and 10 Notes Chapter 9: On the Training of the Senses: Chapter 10: The Teacher: What did it teach you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Childhood: Practical Life Album</title>
      <link>http://example.org/album/practical_life/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/album/practical_life/</guid>
      <description>montessoritampa.com
Submitted to: Graduate Faculty of University of Wisconsin River Falls Course Dates: June through August 2021 Created by: Stephanie Thompson 1340 Orange Street, River Falls, WI (715) 977-0686 stephanie.thompson@myuwrf.edu Table of Contents Practical Life Rationale References Introduction to Practical Life Are Montessori Schools Good for Kids With Sensory Issues? What Is Sensory Processing Disorder? Sensory Development The Montessori Classroom Practical Life Activities References About the Author SPD and Montessori Practical Life (Gross Motor) Grace and Courtesy Lessons I.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://example.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 09:03:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Author: Stephanie Thompson
Web Admin: Mawt</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Albums</title>
      <link>http://example.org/album/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/album/</guid>
      <description>Practical Life
Sensorial
Math
Language
Art Music Movement
Culture</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
